This is my renal lodge, I place it above my renal lodge.
这是我的肾窝，我将其置于肾窝上方。
I am in the axis behind here of the omental bursa and all this relationship of
我位于网膜囊后腔的后方轴线上，以及所有这些与
the stomach,
胃的关系，
but in its posterior part.
但其后部。
This growth movement of my liver will perform all this movement
我肝脏的这种生长运动将产生所有这些运动，
of sub-diaphragmatic tilting
膈下倾斜运动，
and gastric placement, but also, we
以及胃的定位，但我们也会
go further, what is called,
更进一步，也就是我们所说的，
the retro-gastric pouch, the placement of the devil.
胃后囊（即网膜囊）的定位，以及十二指肠的定位。
of the omentum, of the spleen, etc., will depend on this enormous growth of my liver.
网膜、脾脏等的定位，将取决于我肝脏的巨大生长。
All this system, on a fascial level, and this is a reference axis that we must have,
整个系统，在筋膜层面上，这是一个我们必须具备的参考轴，
is suspended from my aorta.
悬挂于我的主动脉。
This is where all the trophic gateway passes.
那是所有营养通道的所在。
It's as if it also revolves around the aortic system, you see?
就像它也围绕着主动脉系统旋转，你明白吗？
As if there was an aortic axis here, and the balance point will be made around here.
就像这里有一个主动脉轴，而支点将在此处周围形成。
And you see how the stomach, finally, will, with this movement, follow
你看胃最终如何在这个运动中，遵循
this process.
这个过程。
I brace myself like this, then I come slightly above
我这样固定自己，然后我稍微向上方移动，
the rib cage here, and there, I have, in fact...
在这里的肋弓上方，实际上，我在这里有...
Thank you.
谢谢。
I'm exaggerating the movement for you.
我为你们夸大这个动作。
This is its pure developmental movement.
这就是它纯粹的发育运动。
I'm going to listen embryonically.
我将进入一种偏向胚胎学层面的倾听状态。
First thing, my neutral.
首先，我的中立位。
My hands are placed and encompass well, lightly.
我的双手轻柔地放置并良好地包覆。
The image is ants.
意象是蚂蚁。
You shouldn't kill them, but they shouldn't leave.
既不能杀死它们，也不能让它们离开。
In my head, I have the vascular axis.
在我脑海中，有血管轴。
aortic behind. I have the end of the exhalation, I enter and I
后方的主动脉。我处于呼气末，我进入并
wait. I put myself in this
等待。我置身于这种
quality. The liver here, it's that it comes to seek something at its source. It
这种品质。这里的肝脏，它正在追溯其源头。
needs to go back a little. I let it. First feeling, instead of
需要稍微回溯一下。我让它去。最初的感觉，而不是
having
拥有
this imprint that makes this movement well, it's not entirely free. So it
这种印记虽然能很好地做出这个动作，但它并不完全自由。所以它
seeks to regenerate something. Point of support here, with my elbow, but not too
试图再生一些东西。这里的支撑点，用我的肘部，但不要太
strong. I give the point of support with my breathing.
强。我用我的呼吸提供支撑点。
primary I let the neutral settle and I let the system come we will
原发性，我让中立态稳定下来，并让系统自行运作，我们将
take the axis of the caval heart in fact it's a little more like this if I
感受腔静脉轴线，事实上，如果我
have to put myself in the movement of consciousness
必须投入其中，感受意识的运动
of space the opening of
空间的开放
space the
空间，这种
perception of this space secondly
对这个空间的感知。第二点，
the notion of the neutral
中立态的概念
of the patient
患者的
when this neutral
当这个中立态
begins to mature
开始成熟
little by little
渐渐地
then the two neutrals
那么这两个中立态
meet
相遇
and this process
而这个过程
becomes the therapeutic process
就成为治疗过程
we are a patient
我们是患者
and as we create
而当我们创造
a space
一个空间
of impatience, there is no such encounter here, there is just this happening.
不耐烦的空间，这里就不会有这种相遇，只会发生这种情况。
The process is there, now I can work.
过程就在那里，那时我就可以工作了。
It's about, at a given moment, daring to let the primary respiration work.
在某个时刻，敢于让原发性呼吸运作。
And there, I know we want to, but we can also do this practice.
而这时，我知道我们都想，但我们也可以很好地进行这种练习。
I sometimes teach, here I'm teaching you a bit
我有时会教，现在我教你们一些
this energetic, embryonic level
这个能量层面，胚胎学的
but we can very well do it
但我们完全可以做到
through fascial planes
通过筋膜平面
etcetera too, no problem
等等，也没有问题
my observation
我的观察是
is that it doesn't hold well
它不能很好地维持